Bhakta Batchala Dash Senior System Engineer

Performance-driven and motivated UI Developer with 4+ years of experience in participating in all phases of software development. Possess strong attention to detail, well-developed time management skills, and the ability to complete all projects within schedule and promptly. Worked with multiple countries with multiple clients such as Visa Technologies, Nets, Rak Bank.

dashlucky248@gmail.com

****** +91-7795149654

Bangalore

Linkedin

Work Experience

Senior System Engineer (React Js)

- Experience in working with Agile methodology.
- Responsible for development of new highly-responsive, web-based user interface using react Js.
- Work with product and UX team.
- Develop a flexible and well-structured front-end architecture, along with the APIs to support it.
- Maintain code and write automated tests to ensure the product is of the highest quality.
- Expertise in hand-coding cross-browser and cross-platform.
- Have domain knowledge in various business systems in, Banking, Blockchain, E-commerce, Payment card industry Domains.
- For analytics point of view doing integration with GTM (Google TAG Manager).

Organizations

- Wipro Technologies (Aug 2019 to till date)
- L&T InfoTech (Feb 2017 to April 2019)
- Digitera Technologies (Mar 2016 to Nov 2016)
- Cannykart Technologies (May 2015 to Jan Feb 2016)

Certification

 PCI Compliance Certification (Payment Card Industry)

Language

English, Hindi, Oriya

Technical Skills

HTML5	***
CSS3	**
Bootstrap	***
JavaScript	***
jquery	***
React.js	***
Redux	***
Webpack	***
Node.js	***
PHP	***
MySQL	***
PHP CMS (Wordpress)	***
Google Analytics & GTM	***

Version Control & Tools

- > GitHub, CVS, Bit bucket
- > Zeplin, Invision app, JIRA, VSTS

Project

Name	Stacker Wallet (Client: Nets,
	Denmark)
Description	Stacker Wallet – A digital
	wallet that will be used for
	making micro payments when
	user wishes to read any
	premium article from Danish
	Merchant site. The entire
	transaction and payment flow
	will be maintained on
	Blockchain using stellar as
	the base platform.

Education

B.Tech in electronics & Communication Engineering

Centurion University (Aug 2010 -Nov 2014)